All right, so after that research,
حسنًا، وبعد البحث،
we now know how to set a click listener onto a list item in the list view.
نعلم الآن كيفية تعيين Onclicklistener في عنصر قائمة في واجهة القائمة.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, and going back to our boxes we have this ListView object
&gt;&gt; حسنًا، بالعودة إلى الصناديق نجد لدينا كائن واجهة القائمة
which contains our list item views.
يحتوي على عروض عنصر القائمة.
And we can call the setOnItemClickListener method and
ويمكننا استدعاء طريقة setOnItemClickListener
pass in a listener object.
وتمريرها في كائن listener.
&gt;&gt; And this on item ClickListener object has a method called onItemClick, and
&gt;&gt; كما أن كائن OnItemClickListener يحتوي على طريقة تسمى onItemClick
it can contain any instructions that we want.
ومن الممكن أن تحتوي على أي مستندات توثيق نحتاجها.
So things like popping up a toast message, or even play an audio file.
بعض الأشياء مثل ظهور رسالة منبثقة أو حتى تشغيل ملف صوتي.
&gt;&gt; Okay. That makes sense.
&gt;&gt; حسنًا، هذا أمر منطقي.
And we're going to be hand-holding the student less, right?
والآن سنقلل الدعم المقدم للطلاب، أليس كذلك؟
&gt;&gt; But I like holding hands.
&gt;&gt; ولكني أود تقليل الدعم المقدم.
&gt;&gt; Jessica.
&gt;&gt; جيسيكا.
&gt;&gt; All right, it's okay, it's okay.
&gt;&gt; حسنًا، وهو كذلك.
Even though this next coding exercise has multiple steps,
ورغم ذلك، فإن تمرين التشفير التالي به العديد من الخطوات،
I'm confident the student can handle it.
وثقتي في الطلاب أنهم قادرون على إتمامه بنجاح.
&gt;&gt; See, that's the spirit.
&gt;&gt; هذه هي الروح.
&gt;&gt; So for this next task, I want you to modify the app so
&gt;&gt; بالنسبة للمهمة التالية، أريد منك تعديل التطبيق
that clicking on a list item plays an audio file.
حيث النقر فوق أي عنصر قائمة ينتج عنه تشغيل ملف صوتي.
&gt;&gt; You can do it.
&gt;&gt; يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك.
&gt;&gt; Earlier we decided we would start off by making it work for a single audio
&gt;&gt; قررنا في وقت سابق أننا سنبدأ بتشغيل ملف صوتي واحد
file and then switch over to the correct audio files for each word.
ثم الانتقال إلى ملفات الصوت الصحيحة لكل كلمة.
So I want to provide you with one audio file for the number word one, lutti.
ومن ثم، أريد تزويدك بملف صوتي للكلمة رقم واحد، لوتي.
So check the notes below the quiz to download that MP3 file and
راجع الملحوظات الواردة أدنى الاختبار لتنزيل ملف بامتداد MP3
only be modifying the numbers activity right now.
وفقط تعديل نشاط الأرقام الآن.
So this is what you app should look like when you're done.
هذا هو الشكل المطلوب أن يكون عليه التطبيق عند الانتهاء منه.
Clicking on any list item should play the same word, lutti.
يجب أن يؤدي النقر فوق أي عنصر قائمة إلى تشغيل الكلمة ذاتها، لوتي.
&gt;&gt; Lutti.
&gt;&gt; لوتي.
&gt;&gt; When you're done with this task, go ahead and check this check box.
&gt;&gt; عند الانتهاء من هذه المهمة، استمر وتحقق من مربع الاختيار.